#### Contact

karimian.anahita@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anahitakarimian-bsn-rn-cnor-7026019b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Critical Care

#### Certifications

Certified Nurse Operative Room (CNOR)

# Anahita Karimian BSN,RN,CNOR

CVOR Thoracic/Robotic Surgery Clinical Coordinator at CHI St. Luke's Health

Houston, Texas

## Summary

Experienced Cardiovascular Surgical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in all CV Procedures, including Robotic Thoracic & Cardiac Surgery, Medication Administration, Service Coordination, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Patient Advocacy. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Texas Woman's University.

## Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health

6 years 11 months

CVOR Thoracic/Robotic Surgery Clinical Coordinator February 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Houston, Texas

CVOR Registered Nurse
July 2013 - Present (6 years 11 months)

Houston Methodist Critical Care Registered Nurse December 2015 - June 2016 (7 months)

Houston, Texas Area

#### **HEB**

Sales Associate Cashier
June 2007 - July 2013 (6 years 2 months)

## Education

Texas Woman's University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2011 - 2013)